# OBED AMOASI

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

## PROJECTS

#### **Numbers to words converter**

www.npmjs.org/package/number-word
An npm package to written in typescript
to convert numbers to its word
correspondent

## **SchoolDesk**

www.schooldesk.cc

A multi-tenant school management system currently operating in Ghana and Dr. Congo

## West African Web Apps Vulnerabilities Research

Published a paper in KNUST journal about the effect and magnitude of vulnerabilities in west African web apps

## MongoDb Identity Server Sample

Built a C# identity server sample with mongo data store. The Auth server Sign up, Account Lockout, 2fa and some more, and it follows the OIDC standard

#### SKILLS

#### **Programming Languages.**

Javascript, Typescript, C#, CSS, HTML, SQL, Python, Java, Kotlin, Swift, C/C++

#### **Libraries & Frameworks**

Angular, Node JS, Express, Django, Flask, J-Query, React Hapi JS, ReactNative, Rx, Retrofit,

#### **Tools & Platform**

MongoDB, MySQL, Git, Azure, .Net, Heroku, GCP, AWS, Netlify, Travis RabbitMQ





obedamoasi.com

+233 50 134 6717 / +233 27 388 6806





github.com/kobbymmo

Self motivated Software Engineer with over 5 years of experience, well versed in Frontend and Backend development with Microservices Architecture. I design scalable test driven applications and with awesome **UX**.

### WORK EXPERIENCE

AUG 2018 - PRESENT

## Senior IT Consultant | Accra

Bee & Bloom Digital - Accra, Ghana

Manage and collaborate with other designers to achieve project goals, usually build back-end and translate mockup into frontend designs for clients' application and internal systems.

OCT 2017 - AUG 2018

## Senior Software Engineer | Remote

iTagTip - Calgary, Canada

Worked with a team of three developers to build the backend of a realtime geo-location application, Set up CI/CD on Azure for fast and Safe Deployment. Developed a suite of frontend applications for iTagTip and built a single sign on Authentication server.

JUL 2017 - OCT 2017

## Frontend Engineer | Remote

SchoolDesk - Accra, Ghana

Implemented and Update the frontend design of a multitenant school management software currently operating in Ghana and Dr. Congo.

MAY 2016 – JUN 2017

## **Software Developer**

ASQII – Kumasi, Ghana

Built frontend of client apps from mockups from designers Built a joke sharing social media app Built the web and mobile application of an event management system

## EDUCATION

2013 - 2017

## **Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering**

Kwame Nkurumah University of Science and Technology – Kumasi, Ghana

## Majors in Software Engineering

Courses: Data Structures & Algorithms, Computer Architecture, Distributed Systems Design, Object Oriented Programming, Computer Graphics, Statistics & Probability.

### INTEREST

Maths, Game Theory, Al/ML, Psychology and Human Behavior, Finance, Photography

### HOBBIES

Travelling, Swimming, Reading, Forex Trading, Financial Analysis, Blogging MAY 2014 - 2015

### **Intern Full Stack Developer**

University Information Technology Services - KNUST, KUMASI

Built a Demo Bus Ticketing platform for inter-city transport system

Designed and optimized Database Schemas

SEP 2016 - OCT 2016

## **Freelance Software Developer**

The Gatsby Magazine – KNUST, Kumasi

Developed a campus based digital magazine for the Gatsby magazine

JUN 2013 - JUN 2017

## Part-time Onsite IT Support | Accra

Agenda Commercial Ltd – Accra, Ghana

Provided IT support for employees of Agenda from different backgrounds whiles providing periodic system checks and ensuring maximum uptime possible.

JUN 2014 - PRESENT

## Volunteer Trainer (Weekends Only) | Traveling

Ghana Robotics Academy Foundation – Accra, Ghana

Trained high school students and below in robotics and STEM education.

Prepare students for local and international competitions